question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In 'Mario Kart 64', Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in 'Clash Royale'.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis "
                    "with a disc drive.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Heroes of the Storm, the Cursed Hollow map gimmick requires players to kill the undead to "
                    "curse the enemy team.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In 'Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed', the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the video game 'Splatoon', the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits "
                    "instead of squids.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    }
]
